CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS AND EVENTS ARE FICTITIOUS
人物、地点、 组织和事件均为虚构
I confirmed that he entered the police station.
我确认他进了警察局。
If he obstructed justice and assaulted a police officer,
如果他妨碍司法公正 并袭击警察
it won't be simple.
这不会简单。
Seek more information.
寻求更多信息。
Yes, boss.
是的，老板。
And discover the suspicions that motivated Hwang Mingoo.
并找出激发黄民浩动机的怀疑。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
No...
不...
Apparently, you were once an athlete.
显然，你曾经是一名运动员。
But today he is a marginal.
但今天他是一个边缘人。
If you cross the line with the police,
如果你越过了警察的界限
you could end up dead.
你可能会死掉。
You laughed?
你笑了吗？
Are the South Korean police a joke to you?
韩国警察 对你来说是个笑话吗？
I already know.
我已经知道了。
I'll take off the badge. How about solving it by beating it up?
我会把徽章摘下来。 怎么样通过殴打来解决呢？
-Calm down, sir. -Come up, son of a bitch!
-冷静点，先生。 - 上来吧，王八蛋！
Come on, bastard!
来吧，混蛋！
-Let me go. -Calm down, sir.
-让我走。 -冷静点，先生。
Get rid of that arrogance.
摆脱那种傲慢。
Or do you want to go straight to jail?
还是想直接进监狱？
As you can see,
如你看到的，
I came to surrender.
我是来投降的。
Skirt. And even?
裙子。乃至？
If you came to surrender,
如果你来投降的话
lift your head and list all your crimes.
抬起头 ，列出你所有的罪行。
I lost control and crossed the line
我失去了控制并越过了界限
when attacking a public servant.
当攻击公务员时。
Sorry.
对不起。
I told you to list the crimes, not apologize, damn it.
我告诉过你列出罪行，而 不是道歉，该死。
I accept any punishment.
我接受任何惩罚。
Enough chit-chat.
闲聊够了。
Who were those people in the hotel room?
酒店房间里的那些人是谁？
Listen here.
听这里。
I'm not interested in fucking a nobody like you, okay?
我对和你这样的无名小卒做爱没兴趣，好吗？
Who were those sons of bitches?
那些王八蛋是谁？
Those who left the hotel room with Jung Gicheul.
和郑基哲一起离开酒店房间的人 。
Who is this?
这是谁？
Who are these fuckers?
这些混蛋是谁？
-I don't know. -Then...
-我不知道。 -然后...
Don't try to take the blame. Just tell me the truth.
不要试图承担责任。 告诉我真相吧。
Who are they?
他们是谁？
I'm a fucking nobody, so I don't know anything.
我他妈是个无名小卒， 所以我什么都不知道。
I just know...
我只知道...
that they invest in my boss.
他们投资于我的老板。
Just that.
只是。
As if! Who invests in a criminal?
仿佛！谁投资罪犯？
And why did investors run away?
投资者为何纷纷出逃？
Just look...
只是看看...
It would be strange not to run away
不逃跑才奇怪
of a police officer who arrives screaming like a crazy person.
一名警察 像疯子一样尖叫着到达。
What the fuck did you say?
你他妈说什么？
Repeat what you said.
重复你说的话。
It seems that you were also an athlete.
看来你也是一名运动员。
Truth be told. Who was once an athlete,
说实话。曾经是一名运动员，
You just become a criminal or a police officer, right?
你只是成为一名罪犯或警察，对吗？
AND?
和？
We are practically the same.
我们几乎是一样的。
Just had a little more luck
只是运气好一点
for holding this position today.
今天担任这个职位。
Police officer, just look at one thing.
警官，请看一件事。
He's acting like a criminal.
他的行为就像一个罪犯。
Damn!
该死！
Don't you feel ashamed, you worm?
你这虫子，不觉得羞耻吗？
Seriously, sir. Let me go!
说真的，先生。让我走！
It's done, bastard!
完了，混蛋！
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
Come here, son of a bitch!
过来吧，王八蛋！
-Sir. -Fucking hell!
-先生。 -他妈的见鬼了！
-Take it here!
-把它拿过来！
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
Stop, sir.
停下来，先生。
-Stop. -Let me go!
-停止。 -让我走！
Stupid son of a bitch!
愚蠢的王八蛋！
Damned hell!
该死的地狱！
Let go of me, idiot!
放开我，白痴！
Take it here.
拿过来吧。
You think you can escape my punches, you fucker?
你以为你能躲过 我的拳头吗，混蛋？
Fucking scoundrel!
他妈的流氓！
Do you think you'll escape my punches, scoundrel?
你以为你能逃脱 我的拳头吗，恶棍？
How dare you?
你怎么敢？
Fucking scoundrel!
他妈的流氓！
-How dare you? -I already asked you to stop!
-你怎么敢？ -我已经叫你停下来了！
Let go of me, idiot!
放开我，白痴！
THE WORST OF EVIL
最邪恶的事
Very good. Let's continue.
非常好。我们继续吧。
Then...
然后...
Who were those?
那些人是谁？
Fuck, I don't know.
他妈的，我不知道。
Holy shit, you piece of shit!
妈的，你个废物！
Do you still think I'm joking?
你还觉得我在开玩笑吗？
What? Are you going to hit me again?
什么？你又要打我吗？
You can hit.
你可以打。
Kill me already, asshole.
已经杀了我了，混蛋。
It can leave. Die, motherfucker.
它可以离开。去死吧，混蛋。
What's going on here?
这里发生了什么？
Is this kind of thing common in the Gangnam Police Station?
这种事情 在江南警察局常见吗？
No sir.
不，先生。
No way.
决不。
Sir,
先生，
May I ask the reason for your surprise visit?
请问 您突然来访的原因是什么？
I came to bring information about a homicide case.
我是来带来 一起凶杀案的情报的。
I heard they were in the middle of an investigation.
我听说他们正在进行 调查。
Yes sir. Involves a missing drug dealer
是的先生。 涉及一名失踪毒贩
known as Manager Cho.
被称为曹经理。
Maybe it's the same case.
也许是同一个案例。
But I can't help a police officer who commits violence.
但我无法帮助实施暴力的警察。
I need to report the assault that just happened, right?
我需要报告 刚刚发生的袭击事件，对吗？
Please sir.
先生，请。
We are sorry for what happened.
我们对所发生的事情感到抱歉。
I will take strict measures to discipline my officers.
我将采取严厉措施 惩戒我的官员。
I ask you to let it go just this once.
我请求你放过这一次。
He heard?
他听到？
I'll be more careful.
我会更加小心。
Take it.
拿去。
What the hell...
我勒个去...
What it was?
这是什么？
They asked me to sign something saying I won't sue them.
他们要求我签署一份声明 ，表示我不会起诉他们。
They said they would release me if I forgot
他们说如果我忘记了他们就会释放我
the aggression.
侵略性。
Listen...
听...
Say.
说。
You know everything, right?
你什么都知道，对吧？
What?
什么？
You saw everything at the hotel.
你看到了酒店​​的一切。
What does the boss do?
老板是做什么的？
What's the deal with China?
与中国有何关系？
Why the fuck did he take you instead of me?
他妈的为什么他要带走你 而不是我？
It's related to drugs.
跟毒品有关系。
My father is an addict, you know.
你知道，我父亲是个瘾君子。
So it's an area that I dominate.
所以这是我主导的领域。
I suspected this shit.
我就怀疑这玩意儿了
Only the three heads are involved.
只有三个头参与其中。
Let's join them, Boss Seo.
让我们加入他们吧，徐老板。
You wanted to get rich.
你想致富。
I'll only earn big if they let me participate.
只有他们让我参与，我才能赚大钱。
We need to participate no matter what.
无论如何我们都需要参与。
If you don't have space,
如果你没有空间，
we take someone out.
我们带某人出去。
Are you serious?
你是认真的？
You deserve to be part of this.
你值得成为其中的一部分。
Nobody cares more than you.
没有人比你更关心。
Seriously, it's a complete injustice.
说真的，这完全是不公平的。
You deserve to get rich.
你值得致富。
Tome.
大部头书。
Good job.
好工作。
Thanks.
谢谢。
He was very lucky, really.
他真的很幸运。
He was being beaten by Hwang Mingoo,
被黄民浩殴打，
and the chief prosecutor showed up just in time.
首席检察官及时出现。
Does your police friend
你的警察朋友吗
Did you touch him?
你碰过他吗？
Were you upset because Seungho was released?
你 因为Seungho被释放而感到不安吗？
There were plainclothes police officers inside that hotel.
该酒店内有便衣警察 。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
Did you happen to see it?
你碰巧看到了吗？
It was just my intuition.
这只是我的直觉。
Did you have that intuition?
你有这样的直觉吗？
Your intuition always gets it right.
你的直觉总是正确的。
Why didn't you unmask the police officer?
为什么不揭开警察的面具？
I can't come up and ask, "Are you a police officer?"
我不能上前问： “你是警察吗？”
You're right.
你说得对。
You can notice their presence.
你可以注意到他们的存在。
Wherever you go, there are always some public servants.
无论你走到哪里， 总有一些公务员。
Plainclothes police, prosecutor
便衣警察、检察官
and that friend of yours.
还有你的那个朋友。
The police officer from the Security Division.
保安科的警察。
Jungbae.
正裴。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
What are your suspicions?
你有什么怀疑？
Well, then...
好吧...
No one gets away with attacking a police officer.
没有人会 因为袭击警察而逃脱惩罚。
So the cops are protecting Seungho?
所以警察 是在保护胜浩？
This is certainly not the case,
事实肯定不是这样的，
but there is something strange.
但有一些奇怪的事情。
Seungho went there in your place.
胜浩代替你去了那里。
Leave it there. Let's enjoy the drink.
把它留在那里。让我们尽情地喝一杯吧。
-Jungbae. -May I help?
-正裴。 -我可以帮忙吗？
There are several inconsistencies in this month's accounting.
本月的会计有几处不一致之处。
Need to tidy up.
需要收拾一下。
Sure, boss. It can leave.
当然，老板。它可以离开。
Jungbae takes care of the company's accounting.
Jungbae 负责 公司的会计工作。
He is very meticulous. I hope he understands.
他非常细心。 我希望他能理解。
Boss,
老板，
What did you decide with the Chinese?
你和中国人做了什么决定？
We are still at an impasse.
我们仍处于僵局。
What if you talked to them?
如果你和他们交谈怎么办？
Forgiveness?
饶恕？
The Chinese woman was interested in you.
那个中国女人对你感兴趣。
Why don't you go out and talk?
你为什么不出去谈谈？
Like this?
像这样？
Seungho is smart and solves things,
胜浩很聪明，能解决问题，
but he is still a newbie.
但他仍然是一个新手。
Especially for something of this relevance.
特别是对于这种相关的事情。
I think this role is yours.
我认为这个角色是你的。
The conversation only flows as equals.
对话只能平等进行。
These ingrates from China and Japan forget
这些来自中国和日本的忘恩负义者忘记了
who only became rich because of me.
他只是因为我而变得富有。
They despised me and insulted me.
他们鄙视我并侮辱我。
They're sons of bitches.
他们是狗娘养的。
I'll handle it, boss.
我会处理的，老板。
I can fix these scoundrels
我可以解决这些恶棍
who insulted you.
谁侮辱了你。
Let's talk about this later,
这个我们稍后再说吧
when Jungbae is here.
当郑培来的时候。
Okay, let's drink.
好吧，我们喝吧。
Kwon Seungho did very well.
权胜浩表现得非常好。
And whether you're with a drug dealer or not.
以及无论你是否与毒贩在一起。
There's no way to help.
没有办法帮忙。
His Japanese godfather thinks he is the king himself.
他的日本教父 认为他本人就是国王。
Will you disobey?
你会不服从吗？
So our agreement came to an end.
于是我们的协议就终止了。
Hello?
你好？
Oi, Euijeong.
哎，义正。
LEE AND BODYGUARDS
李和保镖
I informed the Chinese police about the fake passports.
我向中国警方通报了 假护照的情况。
They will start an investigation too.
他们也将开始调查。
We are almost there.
我们就快到了。
We discovered the intentions of the Chinese and the Japanese.
我们发现了中国人和日本人的意图。
We already know what they plan.
我们已经知道他们的计划了。
Why don't we arrest them soon?
我们为什么不尽快逮捕他们呢？
We can not do that.
我们不能那样做。
And if this Miss. Lee close the drug factory?
那如果这位李小姐 把药厂关了呢？
What if the Japanese insist that they only bought fake glasses and watches?
如果日本人坚持说 他们只买了假眼镜和手表怎么办？
In that case, our only option would be to accuse Jung Gicheul of murder.
那样的话，我们唯一的选择 就是指控郑基哲谋杀。
We just need one more thing.
我们只需要一件事。
Catch them red-handed at the time of negotiation.
在谈判时当场抓住他们。
The problem is that their agreement is hanging by a thread.
问题是他们的协议 岌岌可危。
We can't let it break. We need them to negotiate again.
我们不能让它破裂。 我们需要他们再次谈判。
Drug...
药品...
All good. I'll talk to the Chinese woman.
都好。我会和那个中国女人谈谈。
I want them to fix Choi Jungbae.
我希望他们能修复崔正培。
He's the one who suspects me the most.
他是最怀疑我的人。
I have no idea how he will react.
我不知道他会作何反应。
Let's get him away from Jung Gicheul as quickly as possible.
尽快让他远离郑基哲吧。
I noticed you're worried.
我注意到你很担心。
Can you notice?
你能注意到吗？
In difficult times, you were always quiet.
在困难的时候， 你总是很安静。
Whatever it is,
不管是什么，
I know it will turn around.
我知道事情会扭转。
As he always did.
正如他一贯所做的那样。
In the old days, we would meet at night
以前， 我们会在晚上见面
and talked about everything. Remember?
并谈论了一切。记住？
I remember. And truth.
我记得。和真相。
I know by chance...
我偶然知道...
need help, let me know.
需要帮助，请告诉我。
Why?
为什么？
As?
作为？
Do you want to help me?
你想帮助我吗？
You helped...
你帮...
Seungho too?
胜浩也有吗？
Like this?
像这样？
Anything.
任何事物。
Talking to you makes me feel good.
和你说话让我感觉很好。
Euijeong.
义正.
How do you cope
你如何应对
Missing your mother?
想念你的妈妈吗？
I don't read.
我不读书。
I let the sadness take over.
我让悲伤占据了一切。
It was nice talking to you. Be careful on the way back.
很开心跟你聊天。 回来的路上要小心。
Goodnight.
晚安。
Hey.
嘿。
-Have you eaten yet? -Good...
-你吃了吗？ -好的...
Not yet.
还没有。
For you ma'am.
为了你，女士。
Our!
我们的！
Thanks for the food.
谢谢你的食物。
Very good.
非常好。
Why don't you go to church anymore?
你为什么不再去教堂了？
Ashamed of me?
为我感到羞耻吗？
Don't say that.
别这么说。
What kind of mother is ashamed of her son?
什么样的母亲会为自己的儿子感到羞耻？
Can you do me a favor?
你可以帮我个忙吗？
TAKE AWAY
带走
How can I help you?
我怎么帮你？
Hello?
你好？
Hey.
嘿。
Say.
说。
It's Kwon Seungho.
这是权胜浩。
We saw each other that day at the hotel.
那天我们在酒店见面了。
Clear! So you managed to get away with it?
清除！所以你成功逃脱了吗？
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Do you think I hid a damn bomb?
你认为我藏了一枚该死的炸弹吗？
I remembered. He doesn't speak Korean.
我记得。他不会说韩语。
Damn, so that's how you got away with it?
妈的，你就这样 逃过一劫？
Was a beating enough to solve it?
一顿打就可以解决了吗？
No.
不。
Take good care of her, you hear?
好好照顾她，听到了吗？
So this bastard speaks Korean.
所以这个混蛋会说韩语。
Are you coming from the hotel?
你是从酒店来的吗？
Maybe yes maybe no.
也许是，也许不是。
I understood.
我明白了。
Where do you want to go?
你想去哪里？
Somewhere with lots of land and houses.
有很多土地和房屋的地方。
Who is it?
是谁？
I came to request your services.
我是来请求你的服务的。
We are closed.
我们关门了。
You know me.
你了解我。
I work with Jung Gicheul.
我和郑基哲一起工作。
What do you want?
你想要什么？
I didn't come to ask for anything complicated.
我并不是来询问任何复杂的事情。
You know that woman my boss asked for information from?
你知道我老板向我要信息的那个女人吗？
I just wanted to know
我只是想知道
a little more about her.
更多关于她的信息。
In what sense?
凭什么？
A newbie named Kwon Seungho arrived.
来了一位名叫权胜浩的新人。
He says he went to the same school as Yu Euijeong.
他说他和柳义正在同一所学校。
I want to know if it's true.
我想知道这是不是真的。
I also need to know if she really lived in Wonju.
我还需要知道 她是否真的住在原州。
If she lived there, was she Kwon Seungho's neighbor?
如果她住在那里的话， 她是权胜浩的邻居吗？
I noticed you didn't like my order.
我注意到你不喜欢我的订单。
If you confirm the information, I will pay triple.
如果您确认信息， 我将支付三倍费用。
Hello? It's Cheon speaking.
你好？说话的是陈。
One of your guys came here.
你的一个人来到这里。
Choi Jungbae?
崔正培？
Yes, that's him.
是的，就是他。
Did you mention the other accounting book?
你提到另一本会计账簿了吗？
I only do what you say.
我只做你说的。
I did not say anything.
我什么都没有说。
Your job is to be a tour guide.
你的工作是当一名导游。
Aren't you going to explain things to me?
你不打算向我解释一下吗？
Well, then...
好吧...
That is...
那是...
a roofed house from the Joseon Dynasty.
朝鲜王朝的有屋顶的房屋。
I understood.
我明白了。
And those fish...
还有那些鱼...
Are carps from the Joseon Dynasty?
鲤鱼是朝鲜王朝的吗？
It's a lake from the Joseon Dynasty, so...
这是朝鲜王朝的一个湖，所以...
Didn't you say you wanted to look at real estate?
你不是说想看 房地产吗？
Houses with old roofs are also real estate.
旧屋顶的房子 也是房地产。
Didn't stop here just to find out
并没有停下来只是为了找出答案
if someone followed us?
如果有人跟踪我们？
I thought you only had muscles,
我以为你只有肌肉
but it has a brain too.
但它也有大脑。
Have you finished the inspection?
你检查完了吗？
How about we eat something nice?
我们吃点好吃的怎么样？
Something very tasty and typical.
非常美味和典型的东西。
Seungho, you don't look like a gangster.
胜浩，你看起来不像黑帮啊。
Looks more like a soldier.
看起来更像一个军人。
Don't see me as a gangster.
别把我当黑帮。
see me
看我
as an aspiring entrepreneur.
作为一个有抱负的企业家。
May I ask...
请问...
What part of China are you from?
你来自中国的哪个地区？
Guess.
猜测。
Shanghai?
上海？
Beijing?
北京？
Then...
然后...
When we see each other again,
当我们再次相见时，
I will be sharp in China's geography.
我对中国地理很敏锐。
Why are you so loyal to Mr. Jung
你为什么对郑先生如此忠诚
to the point of risking your life?
到了冒着生命危险的程度吗？
Clear.
清除。
I don't know.
我不知道。
Simply...
简单地...
it comes from within.
它来自内部。
Inside?
里面？
-Yes. -I thought...
-是的。 -我想...
that was in exchange for some property or asset.
这是为了换取一些财产或资产。
No.
不。
I really admire him
我真的很佩服他
and I like him.
我喜欢他。
And my body follows my heart.
我的身体跟随我的心。
What a romantic guy!
多么浪漫的一个人啊！
This is bad?
这不好？
No, on the contrary. I just found it curious.
不，恰恰相反。我只是觉得很好奇。
It's unusual.
这很不寻常。
Then,
然后，
I still don't know your name.
我还不知道你的名字。
Lee Haeryun.
李海润.
What form of treatment should I use?
我应该使用什么形式的治疗？
You can call me whatever you want.
你可以随意称呼我。
Haeryun,
海云,
Will you continue to negotiate with Mr. Jung?
您会继续与郑先生谈判吗？
The accident that happened will never happen again.
已经发生的事故， 不会再发生了。
I will be by Mr. Jung's side to ensure it doesn't happen again.
我会站在郑先生身边， 确保这种事不再发生。
Can bring.
可以带。
We have some Korean informants who work nights.
我们有一些 晚上工作的韩国线人。
They told us where to buy meth.
他们告诉我们 在哪里可以买到冰毒。
If it sinks, it's bad.
如果沉下去了，那就不好了。
If it bubbles, it is of high quality.
如果出现气泡，则说明品质较高。
The quality of this one is excellent.
这一款的质量非常好。
Only we offer this quality.
只有我们提供这种品质。
And what does that mean?
这意味着什么？
Here is a typical dish.
这是一道典型的菜。
Try it.
尝试一下。
Mr. Jung embezzled our products,
郑先生盗用了我们的产品，
that should arrive in Japan,
应该到达日本，
to sell them here in South Korea.
在韩国出售它们。
How to negotiate with someone who doesn't inspire trust?
如何与 不能激发信任的人谈判？
My apologies.
我很抱歉。
I don't know how my boss works.
我不知道我的老板是怎么工作的。
And that?
然后？
Don't you have anything else to say?
你还有什么要说的吗？
No suggestions?
没有建议吗？
Wait, I have a proposal.
等等，我有一个提议。
If you don't trust my boss...
如果你不信任我的老板...
you can trust me.
你可以相信我。
I'll take it to Japan,
我会把它带到日本
in my boss's place.
在我老板的位置上。
Give me a chance.
给我一个机会。
So you're going to betray Mr. Jung?
所以你要背叛郑先生？
I will not betray you.
我不会背叛你。
I will ask his permission
我会征求他的同意
to officially participate in the operation.
正式参与运营。
If I help you make a profit,
如果我能帮助你盈利
there is no reason for him to object.
他没有理由反对。
However,
然而，
what difference does it make to me
这对我有什么影响
for you to be the intermediary?
让你当中介？
The difference is that...
不同之处在于...
if we work together,
如果我们一起努力，
will spend more time with me.
会花更多的时间和我在一起。
Seung Ho.
胜浩
When it comes to work,
当谈到工作时，
What do you think is worth more?
你认为什么更值得？
The heart or the money?
心还是钱？
Gicheul diverts products that go to Japan.
Gicheul 转移 运往日本的产品。
The Chinese discovered that it sells here.
中国人发现 这里有卖。
Cum! The agreement with the Chinese company could end up going down the drain.
暨！与这家中国公司的协议 最终可能会付诸东流。
We need to act.
我们需要采取行动。
Let's stop these drugs from being sold here.
让我们阻止这些药物 在这里销售。
When we resolve this,
当我们解决这个问题时，
I will find a way to convince the Chinese.
我会找到一种方法来说服中国人。
They said they sell the drug at Tae-ho Rock Cafe.
他们说他们在 Tae-ho Rock Cafe出售这种药物。
Let's set up bait for Choi Jungbae
给崔正裴设置诱饵吧
and deliver us from it.
并救我们脱离它。
Let's go!
我们走吧！
Hey, how are you?
嘿，你怎么样？
Okay, let's do it.
好吧，我们开始吧。
Shouldn't they dress better here? What outfit is that?
难道他们不应该穿得更好一点吗？ 那是什么衣服？
Good evening, sir.
晚上好，先生。
OK let's go.
好了，走吧。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
NARCOTICS DIVISION
禁毒处
As for Tae-ho Rock Cafe...
至于泰浩摇滚咖啡馆……
I'm fucking talking to you.
我他妈正在跟你说话呢。
Right.
正确的。
Rumor has it that there's a new drug there.
有传言说那里有一种新药。
-I understood. -"Gangnam Crystal."
-我明白了。 -《江南水晶》。
-And you are the owner of the nightclub. -I am.
-而你是夜总会的老板。 -我是。
Then you must know something.
那么你必须知道一些事情。
Can I have a cigarette?
我可以抽支烟吗？
Do not know?
不知道？
Cum...
暨...
What is this?
这是什么？
Are many.
很多。
You are a very curious guy.
你是一个非常好奇的人。
-It is written in Chinese. -Chinese?
- 它是用中文写的。 -中国人？
Bring a Chinese dictionary.
带一本汉语词典。
Do you want some time to reflect alone?
你想要一些时间独自反思吗？
Are we supposed to wait outside?
我们要在外面等吗？
Of course, no problem. We leave.
当然没问题。我们离开。
Get back to work!
回去工作！
Feel free to read everything and think.
随意阅读所有内容并思考。
The Chinese woman doesn't stop talking about trust.
这位中国女性不停地谈论 信任。
They are considering
他们正在考虑
ask the Japanese to cancel the operation.
要求日本 取消这次行动。
Boss,
老板，
Instead of standing still, we...
我们没有坐以待毙，而是...
Don't let them open their mouths.
别让他们张开嘴。
Gicheul, Jungbae was arrested.
奇哲、正裴被捕。
-What? -And now?
-什么？ -现在？
Damn cops!
该死的警察！
Circling!
绕圈！
Get out of the way.
走开。
Get out of here.
离开这里。
Get down from there!
从那里下来！
Turn off the music.
关掉音乐。
-Let's get them out there. -Group everyone on one side!
-让我们把他们弄出去吧。 - 将所有人聚集在一侧！
-Fast! -Get down from there!
-快速地！ -从那里下来！
This is the police.
这是警察。
Like this?
像这样？
If you cooperate, we won't be long.
只要你合作，我们就不会长久。
Stop now!
现在停下来！
Tramp, don't do anything.
流浪汉，什么都别做。
Turn around and stand still.
转身并站稳。
Get him!
抓住他！
Come here!
过来！
-Hold on tight. -Let me go!
-紧紧抓住。 -让我走！
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈在做什么？
Well, what do you think?
那么你觉得呢？
Treasure hunt.
寻宝。
Here it is.
这里是。
Shit.
拉屎。
Cum...
暨...
Officer Choi.
崔警官。
Man, I'm so envious of these famous people's lives.
哎呀，我真羡慕 这些名人的生活。
Damn...
该死...
Excuse me sir.
对不起，先生。
Chord.
弦。
What...
什么...
What?
什么？
We're from the police.
我们来自警察局。
You logo!
你这个标志！
-How dare you? -Cum!
-你怎么敢？ -暨！
-What? -Get your hands off me.
-什么？ -把你的手从我身上拿开。
I already told you to get out of the way.
我已经告诉过你让开。
Holy shit!
天啊！
-Come on, come on. -Son of a bitch.
-好啦好啦。 -王八蛋。
Ignore people.
不理会人。
Continue thinking.
继续思考。
-What? -Collect your urine.
-什么？ -收集你的尿液。
Who told you about me?
谁告诉你我的事了？
Who was the idiot that told on me?
告发我的那个白痴是谁？
In that other room,
在另一个房间里，
is the owner of Tae-ho Rock Cafe, Choi Jungbae.
泰浩摇滚咖啡馆的老板 崔正裴。
You know who you are.
你知道你是谁。
He also attended Yeoksam High School, right?
他也曾就读于 驿三高中吧？
Shit!
拉屎！
Sir, we're done.
先生，我们已经完成了。
If you're not going to talk, you'd better go home and rest.
如果你不打算说话， 你最好回家休息。
What it was?
这是什么？
You're not a suspect, you're just a witness.
你不是嫌疑人，你只是证人。
If you don't have anything to say, you can go.
如果你没什么可说的，你就可以走了。
-Give me a cigarette. -There is no more.
-给我一支烟。 -没有了。
Go buy. You're rich.
去买。你很有钱。
What did you tell the police?
你跟警察说什么了？
What could I have said?
我还能说什么？
They were the ones who brought it up.
他们是提出这个问题的人。
They talked about rumors of meth sales
他们谈论了 冰毒销售的谣言
and they asked me about it.
他们问我这件事。
And there?
那儿呢？
I did not say anything.
我什么都没有说。
Then they ransacked the nightclub.
然后他们洗劫了夜总会。
So that means...
所以这意味着...
that I am to blame for this?
我应该为此负责吗？
Get out! I need to talk to him.
出去！我需要和他谈谈。
What the hell is that?
这他妈到底是什么？
Gicheul!
吉彻尔！
-Choi Jungbae, bastard! -What is it?
——崔正培，混蛋！ -它是什么？
How dare you tell on me?
你怎么敢告发我？
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
How dare you fuck up the life of a former colleague, you asshole?
你怎么敢搞砸 前同事的生活，你这个混蛋？
What bullshit is this? I didn't tell on anyone, idiot!
这是什么鬼话？ 我没有告诉任何人，白痴！
You told the police that I use drugs, you bastard!
你告诉警察 我吸毒了，你这个混蛋！
Did you go crazy or smell glue?
你是不是疯了或者闻到了胶水的味道？
I didn't tell on shit!
我又没说脏话！
Yeah, I went crazy, broke in!
是的，我疯了，闯了进来！
If it weren't for my lawyer,
如果不是我的律师
I would have fucked myself today, asshole!
我今天真想操自己，混蛋！
Gicheul,
吉彻尔,
fix this bastard!
解决这个混蛋！
Everyone leave except Jungbae.
除了正裴之外，其他人都离开了。
Get out!
出去！
Now that we're alone,
现在我们孤身一人，
tell me the truth.
告诉我真相。
Didn't think it was strange when they released Kwon Seungho,
当他们释放权胜浩时并不觉得奇怪，
But do you find it strange when they let me go?
但是他们放我走的时候你觉得奇怪吗？
I did not say anything.
我什么都没有说。
And why did they release you?
他们为什么释放你？
Seriously, Gicheul, it's done.
说真的，Gicheul，已经完成了。
You know I never lied to you.
你知道我从来没有对你撒过谎。
He is sure?
他确定吗？
Gicheul.
吉舍尔。
It's a second accounting book for the nightclub.
这是夜总会的第二本会计账簿。
Explain.
解释。
-Jungbae. -Say.
-正裴。 -说。
Were you pocketing money?
你把钱装进口袋了吗？
Did you look for my information?
你查过我的信息吗？
Did you really think...
你真的以为...
that I wouldn't find out that you're selling my stuff?
以免我发现 你在卖我的东西？
Your things?
你的东西？
Our things.
我们的东西。
What?
什么？
When the drug runs out, addicts turn away.
当毒品用完后， 瘾君子就会转身离开。
I only stocked up a little as a precaution.
我只储备了一点以防万一。
You should have told me.
你之前应该告诉我。
As if you would agree if I had spoken.
好像如果 我说了你就会同意一样。
Was it for that reason?
是因为这个原因吗？
Then bring what you missed.
然后带上你错过的东西。
Bring it to me.
把它带给我。
Did you think I wouldn't know you were pocketing it?
你以为我不知道 你把它装进口袋了吗？
Take all your money. Go to some very distant interior.
把你所有的钱都拿走。 去一些非常遥远的内部。
And stay away from the police.
并远离警察。
Why?
为什么？
Can't I want to make money too?
难道我也不想 赚钱吗？
I also have ambitions.
我也有抱负。
Why can't I be successful like you?
为什么我不能像你一样成功？
You can do whatever you want,
你想做什么，就可以做什么，
But you can't lie to me.
但你不能对我撒谎。
I understood.
我明白了。
Serious? After 20 years?
严肃的？20年后？
Are you going to kick me out for this?
你要因为这个把我踢出去吗？
It's me you need by your side now.
现在你身边需要的是我。
Gicheul...
吉切尔...
Your perception is distorted. It's Yu Euijeong's fault, the disgusting police officer!
你的认知被扭曲了。 都是柳义正这个恶心的警察的错！
I am wrong?
我错了？
Come to mouth.
来到嘴边。
Otherwise I'll kill you.
不然我就杀了你。
I don't hang around cops. Different from you!
我不跟警察混在一起。 和你不一样！
And she still insists on Kwon Seungho just because he's close to her!
而她还坚持权胜浩， 只是因为他离她很近！
There are strange things happening here,
这里发生了奇怪的事情
but you never suspected him!
但你从来没有怀疑过他！
I'm not the one who should be expelled!
我不是该被开除的人！
It's Yu Euijeong and Kwon Seungho!
是柳义正和权胜浩！
One day, you will realize that you were blind.
有一天，你会发现自己是盲目的。
I guarantee.
我保证。
Look into my eyes.
看着我的眼睛。
You're thinking about a lot of things, right?
你正在思考很多事情，对吗？
Go in peace, sir.
平静地走吧，先生。
You look good in that suit.
你穿那套衣服看起来不错。
Let's go in and take care of the boss.
我们进去照顾boss吧。
Where are you going?
你要去哪里？
He said we needed to move forward or expel someone.
他说我们需要继续前进 或驱逐某人。
Got it, sir.
明白了，先生。
Who is it?
是谁？
It's Kwon Seungho.
这是权胜浩。
In between.
介于两者之间。
Boss.
老板。
Must be upset
一定会心烦意乱
because of Jungbae.
因为正裴。
I know how you feel, but shouldn't we go back...
我知道你的感受， 但我们不应该回去吗？
the negotiations from before?
之前的谈判？
I need to remain firm.
我需要保持坚定。
Yes sir.
是的先生。
Answer.
回答。
Hello? Kwon Seungho speaking.
你好？权胜浩发言。
Hi, it's Haeryun.
嗨，我是海云。
Oi, Haeryun.
喂，海云。
You are with Mr. Jung, right?
你是和郑先生在一起的吧？
I am.
我是。
I was about to call you.
我正想给你打电话呢。
I thought we'd get together
我以为我们会在一起
to clear everything up and talk about future plans.
清理一切 并谈论未来的计划。
How can we think about the future?
我们如何思考未来？
with such an uncertain gift?
带着如此不确定的礼物？
All this confusion started from here. My apologies.
这一切的混乱都是从这里开始的。 我很抱歉。
Aren’t others usually the ones apologizing on your behalf?
别人通常不都是 替你道歉的吗？
If I have time left,
如果我还有时间的话
I will personally accept Seungho's apology.
我个人会接受 胜浩的道歉。
Could it be?
可能是吗？
Just schedule the time.
安排一下时间就可以了。
Wouldn't that be nice, Seungho?
胜浩，这样不是很好吗？
Clear. Just tell me the time, and I'll be there.
清除。只要告诉我时间， 我就到。
I'll call again later.
我晚点再致电。
Let's go out together.
我们一起出去吧。
What does she want?
她要什么？
Whatever it is, it's positive for us.
不管是什么，这对我们来说都是积极的。
Lee Haeryun is giving us an opportunity.
李海润给了我们 一个机会。
Boss,
老板，
I will do whatever it takes
我会不惜一切代价
to make her change her mind.
让她改变主意。
I promise
我保证
that I won't disappoint you.
我不会让你失望的。
Right.
正确的。
I also don't want any more disappointments.
我也不想再有任何失望。
You seem happy.
你看起来很开心。
Can I at least leave in peace?
至少我可以平静地离开吗？
Hey, chubby.
嘿，胖乎乎的。
You always take the easy way out.
你总是选择简单的方法。
That's why he gained so much weight.
这就是他体重增加这么多的原因。
Go down the stairs.
走下楼。
Oh no! The elevator broke.
不好了！电梯坏了。
Holy shit, you piece of shit!
妈的，你个废物！
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
Fucking asshole!
他妈的混蛋！
Boss Seo, wait!
徐老板，等等！
Shit!
拉屎！
You needed a good spanking
你需要好好打屁股
to never think about coming back here again, you piece of shit.
再也别想 再回到这里了，你这个混蛋。
Listen.
听。
Never set foot in this neighborhood again.
永远不要再踏足这个街区。
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
Hey.
嘿。
What is in the church today?
今天教会里有什么？
How about going in alone? I stay here waiting.
一个人进去怎么样？ 我留在这里等待。
It's not good to see us together, right?
看到我们在一起不太好，对吗？
What is happening?
怎么了？
She was very quick in the kitchen.
她在厨房里动作很快。
He got the reputation of being an incredible person.
他被认为是一个不可思议的人。
When they suggested creating a petition
当他们建议创建请愿书时
to bar the institution for people with disabilities,
禁止为残疾人设立机构，
Theresa didn't mince words.
特蕾莎没有拐弯抹角。
And truth.
和真相。
Whenever she saw a child, she would give them a pencil as a gift.
每当她看到孩子时， 她都会送给他们一支铅笔作为礼物。
She had this sweet way.
她有这种甜蜜的方式。
The Theresa Hwang Jinsook I knew
我认识的Theresa黄真淑
shone like a jewel,
像宝石一样闪闪发光，
but he always gave room for others to shine.
但他总是给 别人发光的空间。
And where is dear Theresa now?
亲爱的特蕾莎现在在哪里？
In everyone's memory.
在每个人的记忆里。
Her daughter is here today.
她女儿今天也来了。
Then, take a moment to talk to her.
然后，花点时间 和她谈谈。
Share memories of Theresa with her.
与特蕾莎分享她的回忆。
That way, she will live forever.
这样，她就能永远活着。
We ask that you pour out your mercy
我们请求您倾注您的怜悯
about those who mourn the loss of their loved ones.
关于那些为 失去亲人而哀悼的人。
Surround them with your love and compassion
用你的爱和同情心包围他们
and wipes your tears.
并擦干你的眼泪。
As believers in your life and resurrection,
作为你生命和复活的信徒，
we affirm that death is not the end,
我们坚信死亡不是终结，
but the beginning of a new and eternal existence.
而是一个新的、永恒的存在的开始 。
They didn't need to have done that.
他们不需要这样做。
Of course we needed it.
我们当然需要它。
We have attended church together for over 20 years.
我们一起去教堂 已经二十多年了。
How is your older brother?
你哥哥怎么样了？
He and my son Changdae said they were going to the library,
他和我儿子昌大 说他们要去图书馆，
but they would always get ready.
但他们总是会做好准备。
He is fine.
他没事。
You haven't changed a bit. She looks like the same young woman as always.
你一点也没变。 她看上去还是一如既往的年轻女子。
I was sad that I couldn't go to her funeral.
我很遗憾不能 参加她的葬礼。
But Gicheul asked us
但吉切尔问我们
that we organized this.
我们组织了这个。
Thank you, ma'am.
谢谢你，女士。
You haven't changed a bit. She looks like the same young woman as always.
你一点也没变。 她看上去还是一如既往的年轻女子。
How is your older brother?
你哥哥怎么样了？
He and my son Changdae said they were going to the library,
他和我儿子昌大 说他们要去图书馆，
but they would always get ready.
但他们总是会做好准备。
He is fine.
他没事。
Hello?
你好？
It's Jung Gicheul speaking.
说话的是郑基哲。
Hello, Mr. Jung.
你好，郑先生。
What did Jungbae want to know?
郑培想知道什么？
If Yu Euijeong lived in Wonju,
如果柳义正住在原州的话
if he studied at the same school as Kwon Seungho
如果他和权胜浩在同一所学校读书
and whether they were neighbors.
以及他们是否是邻居。
I want you to discover this.
我想让你发现这一点。
Now?
现在？
I don't think she ever moved to Wonju and always lived in Seoul.
我认为她从未搬到原州 ，而是一直住在首尔。
Sim, Sr. Jung.
西姆，老先生。荣格.
Thanks.
谢谢。
Euijeong.
义正.
Let's stay another hour.
我们再待一个小时吧。
Why?
为什么？
I want to be at peace...
我想要平静...
admiring your face for an hour.
欣赏你的脸一个小时。
Captain Seok called.
石队长打来电话。
He said they are in a cafe.
他说他们在一家咖啡馆。
And where were they before?
他们之前在哪里？
He mentioned a church, but I'm not sure.
他提到了一座教堂， 但我不确定。
-Hello? -Hello, sir. It is me.
-你好？ -你好先生。是我。
Oh, Sr. Lee.
哦，李老师。
That detective Cheon came here.
那个千侦探来了。
He asked me to check
他让我检查一下
whether retired police officer Yu Dukhoon worked in Gangwon.
退休警官柳德勋是否 在江原道工作过？
When I said I couldn't,
当我说我不能的时候
He said he would find out at the Retired Police Officers Association.
他说他会去退休警察协会了解情况。
Will Gicheul take Euijeong hostage...
基彻会 劫持义正作为人质吗……
PRESS
按
I'm writing an essay about former police officer Yu Dukhoon.
我正在写一篇 关于前警官 Yu Dukhoon 的文章。
I need a lot of information.
我需要很多信息。
RETIRED POLICE OFFICERS ASSOCIATION
退休警务人员协会
My workday will end.
我的工作日就要结束了。
Is it urgent?
紧急吗？
I understand. You need to go home, right?
我明白。你需要回家，对吗？
By the way, it seems...
顺便说一下，似乎...
that he was never...
他从来没有...
in Gangwon Province.
在江原道。
It's a great discovery.
这是一个伟大的发现。
Hello.
你好。
Is your name Cheon Jinpyung by any chance?
你的名字是千镇平吗？
It is me.
是我。
You know me, right?
你认识我，对吧？
Mr. Jung sent me here.
郑先生派我来的。
Can we talk for a moment?
我们可以聊一会儿吗？
Clear.
清除。
Why talk in the rain?
为什么要在雨中说话？
By the way, what documents are these?
顺便问一下，这些是什么文件？
These? Why the question?
这些？为什么这样问？
I'm just following orders from my boss.
我只是听从老板的命令。
I'd better ask him.
我最好问问他。
Do not wait.
不要等。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I want to see the documents first.
我想先看看文件。
I already said there's nothing.
我已经说过了，没什么。
Drugs!
毒品！
Holy crap!
碉堡了！
What the hell is that? Give me these documents right away.
这他妈到底是什么？ 立即给我这些文件。
Who are you, anyway?
到底你是谁？
The order came from my boss!
命令是我老板下达的！
Give me those documents now!
现在就把那些文件给我！
Not even fucking that came from him.
连他妈的那句话都不是他发出来的。
This is bullshit. Listen.
这是胡说八道。听。
What makes a police officer pretend to work for a criminal?
是什么让警察假装 为罪犯工作？
Veteran police officer Park Junmo.
资深警察朴俊模。
Genro do Yu Dukhoon.
Genro do Yu Dukhoon。
What confusion are you creating?
你在制造什么混乱？
Cheon Jinpyung, if you continue to be a doormat for bandits,
千镇平， 如果你继续给土匪当受气包，
will end up in prison.
最终会入狱。
I will protect you sir
我会保护你先生
if you cooperate with the police.
如果你与警方合作。
"Cooperar"?
“合作”？
Of course I will cooperate. I'll go the fuck!
我当然会配合。 我他妈的就去吧！
Son of a bitch!
王八蛋！
Cum!
暨！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Help me.
帮我。
Get off of me.
你离我远点。
VETERAN POLICE PARK JUNMO
退伍军人公园军模
Gicheul.
吉舍尔。
I must go now.
我现在必须走了。
See you. Thanks for today.
再见。感谢今天。
The number you dialed...
您拨打的号码...
Subtitles: Tharsis Nóbrega de Araújo
字幕：Tharsis N??brega de Ara??jo